{
    "id": "df3aafd43420421d8df346d08323f661",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………. a nice time on this holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "am having"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is Japanese. She ……………. from Tokyo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "comes",
                "is coming"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. your stay here?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Are you enjoying",
                "Do you enjoy"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. on my computer at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "am working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This semester, I ……………….. chemistry and physics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "study",
                "am studying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. my parents next week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "am visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… to go now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wants",
                "is wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Why ………………….. me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't you understand",
                "aren't you understanding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Smoking …………………. cancer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is causing",
                "causes"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… a lot of films recently.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watch",
                "am watching"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}